PETER:
(WHISPERING) Babe.
LIZZIE: Mmm.
PETER: Lizzie.
LIZZIE: No. Mmm.
PETER:
Come on, please.
LIZZIE: Mmm.
I'm tired, Peter. (EXHALES)
PETER: Baby, come on,
just one.
LIZZIE: Peter.
PETER: Please.
(LIZZIE LAUGHS SOFTLY)
PETER: (SINGING)
♪ Take me to the moon, baby
♪ Take me to the stars
(DOG PANTING)
LIZZIE: (SINGING IN FALSETTO)
♪ Yeah, 'cause you know that
♪ You're mine, baby
(PETER LAUGHING)
♪ You know that you are
(BOTH LAUGHING)
PETER: It's never not funny.
(LIZZIE LAUGHING)
LIZZIE:
You really like it.
PETER: I love it.
(LIZZIE LAUGHING)
(DOG PANTING)
LIZZIE: Mmm. Love you.
PETER: Mmm.
LIZZIE: Oh, yeah.
(DOG WHIMPERING)
PETER: Joyce, off the bed.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
PETER: Oh, you gotta
be kidding me.
Hey.
He stole
my fucking watch.
It's too late
to be calling, Andie.
What?
The guy that I met
at the Hairy Lemon.
We had sex,
he stole my watch,
which cost more than
his fucking car.
Um, I think I have your watch.
What?
You left it here
when you went to the beach.
ANDIE:  Oh.
No. No, fuck it,
it's my Dad's.
I don't give a shit.
I'll talk
to you tomorrow.
ANDIE:  No. Wait.
Can I come over?
Still feels like
this guy stole the watch.
(EXHALES)
ANDIE: Hey, dog.
Didn't realize
you'd stayed over
last night.
Hmm. I should
just rent out a room
from you guys.
Ha.
(LAUGHING)
Hey, you want a muffin?
I got the gross
zucchini kind you like.
You know, I had a friend
who went through
eight rounds of IVF
before she got pregnant.
Okay, maybe
it wasn't eight.
It was more like two.
What are you
talking about?
We should probably
get going.
I don't want you
to be late for therapy.
(LAUGHING) Therapy.
I can't believe
you're in therapy.
I just don't understand
why you have to tell her
everything.
I don't
tell her everything.
Well, she knows
we're doing
another round of IVF,
which, by the way,
was news to me.
I mean, how are we
even gonna pay for it?
We couldn't afford it
the last three times.
Well, I could do
some more tutoring.
That barely
covers groceries.
(SIGHS)
I'm sorry,
I'm sorry.
You know, you don't
have to drive such an
expensive car, Peter.
Well, I have
an image to present
to my clients.
Okay.
I have said from the start
that I would always
be straight with you both.
And I'm willing
to stroke the shaft,
but I'm not gonna
cradle the balls.
Because, the thing is,
this is, um...
This is boring.
Yeah. Really,
I've been watching
the two of you.
You're drowning in the sea
of boring bullshit,
and I am choking
on the fumes.
I mean, you have been coming
in here, I don't know, maybe,
well, over a year,
and I don't think any of us
have really said anything.
It's like
we're talking about
the weather every week.
News flash, it's LA.
It's always sunny.
Nobody gives a fuck.
So, let's focus
on something else.
Thank you,
Dr. Grayson,
thank you.
Previous owner
was a professor of botany,
and he...
You can tell he took care
of his garden,
and rightfully so,
considering
the beautiful vista.
You would probably spend
a lot of time back here.
Now this...
No, you don't want
to get wet?
Hi. This house just
went on the market,
and considering its beauty,
it is probably gonna go
pretty fast.
Where's the pool?
I'm sorry?
(SCOFFS)
This isn't a pool.
It's a fucking petri dish.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hey, Pete!
Don't sweat it.
I know you'll
bring the magic next time.
Ciao,  bella.
Douche bag.
Okay, so let's try,
"He knows her".
Il la connait.
Tres bien, monsieur.
That's great.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(DOG BARKING)
Let's beach it up,
bitch.
I'm just finishing up
here with Justin.
Admit it, you're totally
pulling a Mary Kay Letourneau.
Could you shut up?
What? I want to meet him.
Can I meet him?
Shh!
(DOG BARKING)
LIZZIE: Joyce!
Get it away.
Just ignore her.
Joyce, Joyce.
Justin, this is
my friend, Andie.
Andie? Hey!
LIZZIE: Hey.
LIZZIE: Andie, you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll be right out.
Hey.
Do you think maybe
you've got food poisoning?
No.
(DOG BARKING)
Are you
warm enough?
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
I'm sorry, Lizzie.
What?
Why?
Because,
this is just so unfair.
Hey. It's gonna
be all right.
We're gonna figure this out.
So, who's the guy?
Someone she met
on the internet?
No, it's just somebody
she met in a bar.
(LAUGHS)
Jesus.
So, what's she gonna do?
(EXHALES)
Well, she doesn't know.
PETER: Come to bed.
I told my father.
What'd he say?
He said he'd support me
whatever I decided.
And then he needed
to go play golf.
You know, I really don't
want to have a baby,
but to get rid
of it at my age
seems a little gauche.
(GIGGLING)
Well, you don't
have to tell anyone.
No one would have
to know.
You'd know.
Here you are. Four sugars.
Mmm-hmm.
Ah, sure
you don't want
anything to eat?
We've got
an hour.
No, coffee's fine.
So, how's
your new roommate?
He sucks.
Talks too much in group.
He's got a goiter.
Goiter?
Is that a thyroid issue?
He's got this huge
fucking bulge right here.
And he likes to fondle it,
so it looks like
he's jerking off his neck.
Wow.
So, you need me
to bring you anything?
No, thanks.
Okay.
All right, well.
Take it easy.
Yeah, you too, bro.
Don't call me "bro".
PETER:
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I was just, uh,
thinking of, uh,
starting dinner.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hey.
ANDIE:  Hey.
I want you to have it.
Have what?
The beast growing inside me.
Andie.
Look, I know
this sounds crazy...
Yeah.
It does.
Just listen, okay?
I made an appointment
at the clinic,
but I couldn't
go through with it.
Not when I know
how much you want this.
I can do this for you.
And I want to.
Just think about it.
I,
I don't know what to say.
Say "yes".
LIZZIE: Yes.
I'm sorry, she wants
to just give
us her child?
I know it sounds
a little unconventional...
No, it doesn't, no, no.
People give each other
children all the time.
If anything is passe
at this point...
Mmm. You didn't get
the tiramisu?
What about the father?
Shouldn't he have a say
in this?
She doesn't know
how to get in touch
with him.
She doesn't even know
his last name.
PETER: Of course.
LIZZIE: Why can't we
at least explore this?
PETER: Joyce! Well, because
it's not an expedition.
We're not fucking pioneers.
I can't even believe we're
talking about it. You know
what? It's an insane idea.
PETER: Joyce!
There she is.
LIZZIE: She's here.
PETER: Come here, girl,
come on.
PETER: Jesus! She shit
on the floor again.
LIZZIE: Oh, God, it's 'cause
she's been stuck
in the house all day.
PETER: Yeah, well,
she needs to be
trained properly.
Come on.
ANDIE:  What if he doesn't
come around?
Oh, he'll be fine.
He just needs
a little time to get
used to the idea.
So, I'm gonna
see you later, right?
If you're lucky.
Happy Birthday.
Piss off.
♪ The train is gone, love
♪ It's gone
♪ It's out of sight
PETER: Where did it go?
LIZZIE: (LAUGHS)
I don't know.
♪ Good night, my darling
Whoo!
♪ Darling good night
♪ Good night
Yeah!
Whoo! Whoo!
Hey, um, I'm gonna, um
give you
your present now.
Whoo!
Ooh, I am so excited!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Oh, my God!
(ANDIE LAUGHING)
I was trying
to finish it on time.
I'm sorry, come again?
I made it.
You made it?
(PETER LAUGHS)
LIZZIE: Yeah.
That is disgusting!
Yeah, yeah,
being unemployed
has its benefits.
Look at this!
It's fucking cable knit,
people!
Like, Jesus,
is there anything
you can't do?
Um.
Um, just.
Anyone want any coffee?
Are you sure?
Some tea?
You okay, babe?
LIZZIE:
Yeah, I'm fine.
I love you, lizard.
Oh, I can't take this,
this is too unfair.
ANDIE: Oh, God.
Hey.
Can I?
Sure.
(HEART BEATING)
Wow.
You don't expect it
to be so fast.
I guess when you have
that much growing to do,
your heart's gonna work
twice as hard.
I love you, Lizzie.
I love you, too.
Come on, you guys.
ANDIE: So gross.
Ew, Mom, stop.
You're already
suffocating me.
(BOTH GIGGLING)
Mom.
Mommy.
I need a drink.
LIZZIE: Get me out of here.
ANDIE: You're a bitch,
you're going to be
a terrible mom.
I just don't understand
why she has to live here.
It's just while she's
pregnant, sweetie.
She's all alone.
(DOG BARKING)
No, no, no,
get away from me.
No, no, no, no, no.
Get away from me.
ANDIE: Freak show.
I don't know
what's gonna
happen to me.
What?
I don't want
to be alone.
Andie,
you're not.
Oh, come on,
you know
what I mean.
(SIGHS)
You're gonna find
somebody one day.
I know it.
How do you know it?
God.
I just do.
Like I always knew
that I was gonna be
a mom one day.
Oh, Jesus.
I'm sorry.
I'm so gassy.
(CHUCKLING)
Oh, my God.
Gaseous Clay
over here.
Yeah, it's flying
like a butterfly.
It's floating
It's gross.
Oh, thank God
you get my jokes.
Always, my love.
Hey, make sure
that gate locks
behind you
'cause Joyce
almost got out
the other day.
ANDIE: Leave the gate open.
Cool. Got it.
LIZZIE: Uh, not funny.
God, that baby
looks like
it's uncomfortable.
Hi, I'm Betty.
I'm a sonogram technician.
LIZZIE: Hi.
ANDIE:
What's up, Betty?
No cell phones in here.
Oh. Okay.
Just try to relax.
Hey, when can we
find out the sex?
Wait, wait,
I don't want to know.
Okay. You can
whisper it to me.
No.
No, why?
You can't know if I don't.
Why do you even care?
I don't know. Maybe I'm just
curious if there's a penis
or a vagina growing inside me.
Just forget it, okay?
We don't want to know.
We'll be able to tell
around 14 weeks,
so you two have time
to think about it.
Okay, thank you.
Cool beans.
Cool beans?
Did I just say that?
All right.
This will feel
a little cold.
(ANDIE CLEARS THROAT)
Feels like
I'm getting kissed on.
Andie.
Sorry.
All right,
see that there?
That's the embryo.
Yeah, everything was great.
Doctor said everything
is fine.
We got a little picture
to show you.
Great, great,
sound's good.
Hey, listen, I got a call
from Casey's sponsor.
Oh.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, everything's fine.
Um, he said
Casey can come home.
So, I thought it might be nice
to have him over for dinner.
Oh. Um.
Of course.
Ew. Why are my hands
all sweaty?
I'll just throw
a couple of things
on the grill.
Okay, well, I'll,
I'll make a little salad
or something.
Seriously, I feel like
Clammy Davis Junior.
Okay.
Feel.
Feel that.
Oh, Andie!
That's like totally...
Gross!
I know.
Hey, sweetie,
yeah, I got to go. Bye.
You made it!
Got everything?
Okay, let's do this.
(SIGHS)
Jesus,
that guy is totally
gonna relapse.
Andie, don't say that.
ANDIE:
Mmm-hmm.
(GIGGLES)
Hi, boys!
ANDIE: Okay, again, fast.
Faster, one, two, three.
(LIZZIE LAUGHS)
ANDIE: Yes!
This is coming
straight at you
this time, okay?
LIZZIE: One, two,
three. Yes!
Awesome!
Hey, both of you
do me a favor.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Guys, let's not
tell Casey
about the baby, yet.
Why?
What am I gonna say?
Sorry, you just
got out of rehab
for the fourth time,
but guess what?
We're getting a baby.
Okay. Just seems
a little weird
if we don't tell him.
Well, I just want to give him
some time to adjust
to his new surroundings.
Then, we'll tell him.
Okay.
Andie?
Sure, dog.
It's your party.
Hey, can you make
one of those
well done for me?
Oh, Jesus!
Joyce, took a shit
on the floor again.
It's because she's not
getting enough praise
when she goes outside, honey.
She took a dump
upstairs, too.
Yeah, and did you
clean it up?
Joyce, I'll shit
in your dog house tonight.
(DOG WHIMPERS)
How's the tri-tip, bro?
It's fine, bro.
Mmm, it's great, honey.
You know, I always
wanted to go to rehab.
I mean, not to get sober.
Do you like that corn,
Casey?
It's, it's from the garden.
Mmm, yeah, thanks.
Hey, so, any news
on the baby front?
Um, no, not yet.
Who's up for dessert? Huh?
LIZZIE: Sure.
Yeah.
I don't see
why you guys
don't just adopt?
Or did Mom and Dad's
whole experience
put you off that idea?
You done with that?
I mean, just cause
I'm a bad apple.
Sorbet, do we have any?
LIZZIE: Yes.
We do. Good.
Honey, we've even got some
ice cream in the freezer.
We do. That's right. Great.
I will get that then. Good.
And how about tea? Coffee?
PETER:
Anyone? I'll do that.
I'll make a pot of both.
And decaf for you.
No, you can have caffeine.
I'm sorry.
All right.
And I'll be right back.
Okay.
So, what are you saying?
He wants to move in here?
No, no, no, no, no.
It's just his doctor
doesn't think
he should be alone right now.
Doesn't he have any friends
that he could stay with?
All of his friends
are drug-addicts.
Just.
I don't think
this is a good idea.
Well, then this isn't fair.
Andie gets to stay here.
(SIGHS)
I'm sorry.
Look, I just
want to be able
to keep an eye on him.
Okay?
Of course.
Of course,
he can stay.
Thank you.
(SIGHING)
Can you take
this thing off?
Ooh, of course.
Please. Peter.
Okay. I'm gonna go
make up the couch.
Thank you.
Joyce.
Babe?
That's an expensive
cut of meat.
It's not for Joyce.
(DOG WHIMPERS)
Here.
It's good, expensive meat.
ANDIE:
Casey needs to grow up.
Mmm.
So you got adopted,
you know? Get over it.
Come on,
he's just sensitive.
Sensitive?
My tits are sensitive.
(GIGGLES)
Is what he said true?
Is Peter afraid
of getting a bad apple?
What? No!
No. I'm serious.
Maybe he's afraid
I'm carrying a demon-child.
Well, I'm certainly
starting to be.
Mmm.
Hey, sweetie.
LIZZIE: Hey.
Where are you guys going?
We're going to play b-ball.
Honey, the gates.
Got it. I'll fix it tomorrow,
I promise.
Come on, Casey,
get the ball.
I don't know
if we're gonna
make the game, bro.
Please stop calling me
"bro", please.
You sound like a jackass.
You know, maybe
we could just go
to a meeting instead, huh?
Here we go.
PETER: What?
Just leave me alone, Peter.
All right? Stop it.
Look, I'm sorry, Casey,
but I'm not gonna do that.
Cause I made a promise
to Mom and Dad...
You promised Mom and Dad.
(SIGHS)
Whoa, whoa,
can you not?
Jesus Christ!
I don't know what to do.
No, I get it, okay.
I, I put everyone
through hell.
I didn't say that.
All the stress I caused
gave Dad a stroke
and Mom cancer
and I'm
a fucking asshole.
I didn't say that!
All right?
Might as well.
Jesus, just forget it.
We'll go to the movies.
(SIGHING) All right.
(ICE CREAM TRUCK JINGLE)
Hey, you want ice cream, bro?
Seriously, I'm gonna
kick the shit out of you.
(INAUDIBLE)
WOMAN: Mommy knows
you're frustrated.
WOMAN: I know, sweetheart.
You must use your words.
Use your words,
sweetheart.
God! "Use your words"?
That is so fucking
patronizing.
Don't you ever say that
to this kid, Lizzie.
PETER: Five bedrooms,
if you count
the guest-house.
Banister you're holding onto,
recently reinforced.
Brand new,
as a matter of fact.
Now, my favorite spot
in the entire house.
You'll immediately see why.
Because, the view,
which is so spectacular,
takes in most of...
Yeah, no, it's...
It's too white.
Too white, right.
Well, you could paint it.
Yeah, you know what?
I actually
can't even be here anymore.
It's burning out my retina.
(LAUGHING)
Right.
We got vertigo.
Wow. Vertigo.
The...
Okay, Pete.
The view
can only really...
Yep.
You know, be appreciated
when you look at it.
(DOOR SHUTS)
(SIGHS)
(GLASS SQUEAKING)
(ENGINE STARTING)
Hey, Pete. Okay.
I'm sporting baby trout
right now.
I need a house
that's gonna make me hard.
Ciao,  bella.
GIRL: Whoo!
Fuck you!
LIZZIE:  Look at my legumes.
Aren't they beauteous?
It looks like
an engorged scrotum.
Yeah? Look at that.
Wow.
That looks like a good time.
Lizzie, do you have any
interviews lined up?
Uh, no, not yet.
We're not gonna make
our mortgage this month.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I could start
selling drugs again.
Yeah, not funny!
(ANDIE LAUGHING)
CASEY: Come on, Joyce.
How much
do you need?
I could ask my Dad.
Casey, don't get her
riled up.
All right?
Come on. Yeah.
Seriously,
I can make a call.
No, that's okay. Thanks.
Joyce, where's that ball?
Oh! That's a good dog.
Casey, outside!
All right?
What the hell
is going on
in this house?
CASEY: Come on, Joyce.
Get it.
(LAUGHING)
Hey, sweetie.
Mmm.
Will you sing for me?
Not tonight, hon.
I'm really tired.
Okay.
I love you.
Love you, too.
You know what?
I think we should just
go with Vanilla Dream. Hmm?
Mmm. Sounds like
a porno color.
Honey, do you like
this color for
the baby's room?
Where's Casey?
Uh.
I don't know.
He said he'd be back later.
Great.
He's probably with a girl.
You know, he's supposed to
keep his dick in his pants
for the first year,
Honey, he might
have just gone
to a meeting.
Whatever.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Peter?
Don't you think it's time
we just told him
what's going on?
I mean, Andie's gonna
start showing soon.
Okay, I, I am
gonna tell him, but
when the time is right.
PETER:
I just don't want to
make him feel like
a bigger loser
than he already is.
Peter!
Than he already feels like,
that's what I meant.
I feel like
I'm having a boy.
I hope he's gay.
Why?
Well, then when we dress
him up as a doll,
he won't be an asshole
about it.
(GIGGLES)
PETER: Hey.
We're not dressing him up
like a doll.
He's not gonna be gay.
What if he is gay, Peter?
You're not gonna
love him then?
But I might be
and he might wind up
being a butt pirate,
so you need to
fucking come to terms
with that.
Why are we
even talking about it?
You're not gonna be part
of the child rearing!
Are you?
What?
What the fuck
does that mean?
Lizzie, where are you going?
I'm just gonna go
do some gardening.
I know
what you're gonna say.
I need you
to get the threats
under control.
I know.
Sorry,
I can't help it.
I'm sorry,
did I wake you?
PETER: No.
Too tired to sleep.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Do you think
you could ask Andie
for a loan?
If we really need to.
Thanks.
And if you see my testicles
hiding anywhere,
let me know.
I'm gonna see you
same time next week, right?
Okay.
Hey, um, Justin,
do you have any friends
who might need tutoring?
I don't know.
Well, could you ask?
Because I can teach
English and Math, too.
Okay. Sure. See ya.
See ya.
Bon travail, aujourd'hui.
(SIGHS)
(KEYS JANGLING)
Oh! Gross!
It's still warm.
Peter!
Honey, come on!
We're gonna be late!
PETER: Be there in a sec!
How many pairs of shoes
does he have?
It's like you married
a little girl.
That's funny.
Okay.
All right, well.
All right.
Have fun.
Okay. Well, thanks Casey.
Be good.
Hey.
Look at all the produce
I got at the farmer's market.
Oh.
What's that?
This?
Yeah.
It's a kiwi.
Oh, jeez.
Are you crazy?
Andie, I'm not gonna go
cutting into a kiwi!
Okay, freak.
Peter! Come on!
We're gonna hit traffic!
Uh, hello!
Where are you going?
Oh. Right.
Peter's boss has given us
his house in Palm Springs
for the weekend.
What?
Andie, would you calm down?
It's gonna be fine.
Well, that's easy
for you to say.
Andie, come on.
PETER: Sweetie,
do we have enough water?
Yeah, we have
a whole case full, honey.
You sure I shouldn't just
get someone
to fix the gate?
No, no, no.
I'm not paying
someone to fix it.
All right? I'll fix it
when we get back.
(YOWLS)
Everything's gonna be fine.
Hey, maybe I'll go halfsies
with Casey
and get him eight ball, huh?
Splurge on some hookers.
Yeah.
Come on, sweetie.
I want to beat traffic.
LIZZIE: Don't forget
to feed Joyce!
As if I'm not gonna...
Fine.
PETER: And we're off.
(SIGHS)
Hey.
I'm gonna go to the store.
Do you want anything?
Milk, sugar,
crystal meth?
What?
(LAUGHS)
I'm sorry.
(LAUGHING)
That is not funny.
I don't know
why I just said that.
I'm gonna go.
Seriously, that was not fu...
(SNORTS)
(LAUGHING)
(SIGHS)
Why don't you
just put 'em
in the dishwasher?
I'm not allowed.
Under strict orders.
He's such a cheap bastard.
No, he's just going through
a hard time.
Yeah, but he's
a cheap bastard.
(DISHES CLATTERING)
You ever meet
your birth mom?
No.
I even tried to call her
once, but she didn't want
to talk to me.
Maybe you should
just send her an e-mail.
Yeah, well, I can't.
She killed herself
on her 21st birthday.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, my God.
That is so fucked up.
I'm sorry, that's...
That is so not funny.
Do you like ping pong?
CASEY: Uh.
ANDIE: Ooh!
All right, all right.
This is it, game point.
Serve it up.
Okay.
Hey, Casey,
Oh, you're so dead.
Watch out.
There's a DEA agent
behind you!
Whoo!
You suck, motherfucker.
You talk a lot of smack.
At least I don't do
a lot of smack.
Whoa, whoa.
Whoo!
Way out of line.
All right, all right.
Let's bring it, Sid Vicious.
Yeah?
Show me what you got.
You got the skills
for this?
What? What?
Don't you fake me out.
Just having...
Oh!
In the tit!
I just hit you
in the tit.
That's so funny.
You got spoked!
I love curly straws, man.
Mmm.
Seriously, they make
every beverage taste better.
(SLURPING)
Totally.
Here.
What? No.
I want you
to have it.
No.
No, it's your curly straw.
I can't take that.
Seriously,
I want you to have it.
No.
Take it.
Okay.
Wow.
Wow, man.
I just want you to know
that whenever I suck on this
I'm gonna think of you.
(GIGGLES)
Mmm.
Oh, yeah, fuck.
Holy fuck.
Oh, my God.
You're licking my balls.
You're licking
my fucking balls.
You are such
an awesome person.
Oh, my God.
That's it.
How do you know?
You're like reading
my fucking mind.
Oh.
You're like
a sexual clairvoyant.
Oh, my God! Yeah.
(MOANING) Faster.
Faster.
Not the head push.
I hate the head push.
No. Yep, you got it.
No head push.
Here I am.
Oh, that's it.
Oh, faster.
What the fuck?
No hands, no hands.
Uh-huh.
Oh, my God!
I'm gonna fucking come.
Oh, I'm gonna
fucking come.
Holy fuck!
I'm fucking coming!
I'm gonna come right...
Holy fuck!
(PANTING)
What the fuck
are you doing?
LIZZIE: Oh!
Oh, fuck!
Oh!
Jesus!
Oh, my God.
Get the fuck out of here!
You get the fuck
out of here!
It's my fucking house!
Oh! Andie,
what are you doing?
Did you swallow?
PETER: I told you
it was a bad idea
to leave them alone.
Because you thought
they'd do drugs together,
not because she'd turn
into Fellatio Alger!
Who?
I think she meant
Horatio Alger.
Horatio Alger. He wrote
about the American dream
in the 19th century.
You can read?
Oh, my God.
I'm so well read.
I told you
he shouldn't
stay here.
You didn't
listen to me.
What was I supposed to do?
He can't live on his own.
He's proven that
over and over again.
LIZZIE:
So, find another solution.
There is no other solution!
Fuck this.
Casey, wait.
You know, listening
to you guys argue
really makes me question
whether or not you can handle
raising this kid.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
You're pregnant?
We were going
to tell you.
I said that
we should have
just told him.
And you're giving
your baby to them?
Are you out of your mind?
LIZZIE: She's thinking
of what's best
for the child.
And you all think
this is what's best.
Jesus Christ!
I know I win contest
for biggest fuckup
in the room,
but at least
I'm a drug addict.
What's your excuse?
PETER:
Casey, come on.
Casey?
Peter, where are you going?
I'm going to Casey's.
He shouldn't be left alone.
Maybe we should
just give him some space.
No, I'm not going
to give him some space.
Whenever I give him space,
he winds up
snorting horse tranquilizers.
And you, what the hell
were you thinking?
He just got out of rehab.
Sweetie, calm down.
Don't tell me to calm down.
No one should have that
image burned into their brain.
He's my brother.
Not really.
I'm sorry.
That was fucked up.
I didn't mean that.
Peter!
LIZZIE: She just laughs
when she's uncomfortable.
It's like
she has a nervous tick.
She's a lunatic!
And that baby
is going to be a lunatic.
Don't go!
You're not alone!
You got old cock sucker
to lean on.
Joyce, inside, okay?
Joyce.
Come on, Joyce.
Joyce!
(DOG PANTING)
Lizzie,
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean for anything
to happen with Casey.
I mean, clearly, he's,
he's a little gross.
It was a moment
of weakness.
I'm just tired
of feeling alone, okay?
You feel the same way.
Jesus, you can't even
eat a meal by yourself!
Lizzie, wake up!
Peter doesn't want this kid.
He doesn't want kids, period.
Jesus Christ!
Will you say something?
Use your fucking words!
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Hey!
Hey.
Is Lizzie here?
Yeah, just, uh.
One sec.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
ANDIE: Lizzie.
Justin's here
for his lesson.
ANDIE: Hey.
She's not feeling well.
I'm sorry you had to come
all the way down here.
Is she okay?
Yeah, yeah,
she's totally fine.
She's just.
She went on
a bender last night.
You know how that is, right?
Okay. Um.
Is it okay if I stay
here for a little bit?
My dad's not
picking me up
for another hour.
Oh!
Okay.
Game point.
I know.
You don't have
to keep saying that.
I'm not.
I just said it once.
All right, just serve.
That's bullshit!
Sorry.
God, how are you
so good?
(CAR HONKING)
I think that's my dad.
Oh, that's convenient.
What are you guys,
like, father and son drifters?
You know what?
I gotta go,
but I'll see you later.
I'm onto you.
You're a hustler, kid.
That Justin kid
is sweet.
You still mad at me?
I was thinking,
what if there is something
wrong with Casey's jizz.
Could I hurt
the baby somehow?
Come on, Joyce.
I'm serious.
Who knows where
that cock's been?
I mean, what if he's got
an STD or something?
Oh, Jesus!
Maybe I should go
get my stomach pumped.
Who are you, Rod Stewart?
I mean, how much
did you swallow?
I don't know, man,
I didn't have
a measuring cup with me.
I don't understand
why you didn't
just spit it out.
I guess I just got
swept up in the moment.
He was so appreciative.
He'll called me
a sexual clairvoyant.
What did you do?
Oh.
I'm not going
to do that.
LIZZIE:  Look, Peter.
I know this
is a little uncomfortable,
but some of the sites
are saying it can affect
the baby adversely.
I'm not asking him
how many STDs
he just passed on
to Andie
and her unborn child.
Our unborn child,
that's what I meant.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
CASEY: What are you doing in
there? I got to take a shit.
Okay,
I'll be right out, bro!
You know, I'm going to fucking
bust down the door
and shit on your head.
(CHUCKLING) Okay.
You bet, buddy.
No fucking way!
Okay, come on.
What?
Come on, let's go.
Why? Because you're the one
who decided to gargle
Casey's balls, that's why.
Gargle balls!
(GIGGLING)
Ooh, is this
where Casey lives?
Mmm-hmm.
Do you think
it's all dark and druggy?
I don't know.
It just looks like
a guy lives there.
Needs a woman's touch.
Yeah, too bad
I blew that one.
Hey, Peter, could you
come down, please?
I really need to...
Oh, wow, this looks
like it's going
to be good.
It was her,
not me.
What?
I had nothing
to do with this.
I swear, it was her.
Oh! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
LIZZIE:
Oh, dear God!
(GASPING) Oh!
ANDIE: Jesus!
LIZZIE:
Jesus, Casey!
ANDIE: God,
Peter's out of shape.
Open the door!
God! Okay, okay, okay.
Come on!
Oh, my God!
Let me in!
Jesus Christ!
Is he on drugs?
Lock the door!
Go! Go! Drive!
Oh, my God,
he's on drugs!
Oh, my God!
Drive the car!
Please!
LIZZIE: Jesus!
He's not rational!
(SCREAMING)
There!
ANDIE: What's that?
My HIV test.
Look at the date!
From one month ago.
You see? I am clean.
You don't have
to worry about the baby.
Well, that's great!
How do we know
those tests aren't fake?
LIZZIE: Andie!
PETER: Are you insane?
Lighten up!
Leave him alone!
Listen, I'm seriously
happy you don't have AIDS.
Fuck you, man.
Fuck you so hard.
The baby
doesn't have AIDS.
Thanks, Peter.
Fuck you guys.
ANDIE:
See you later, dude.
LIZZIE: Let's just go.
Are you okay, Peter?
God, I'm glad
he's not back on drugs.
I'm winded.
Jesus Christ!
I don't even understand
why this arrangement
is even an issue.
Usually it works out
so well when friends give
each other their babies.
I think if we could
just set some
better ground rules.
No, Lizzie, forget it.
I don't want her
in the house anymore.
The only reason
you have the house
is because of me.
Wait, what?
She paid for your house?
Sorry.
It was supposed
to be a secret.
This is the place
that we tell
our secrets, Peter.
(DR. GRAYSON CHUCKLING)
I have to admit,
that one is a, is a doozy.
She bought
your house and she's
giving you a baby?
Right? Wow, I mean,
I'm starting to feel
kind of gypped here.
Hey, buddy,
I rocked your world!
Wait. Must we? Just.
Okay, you, with the hair,
why are you here?
I? (CLEARS THROAT)
I'm here because
there's concern
amongst some
that I might
start taking drugs again.
Well, frankly,
who could blame you?
Who are you?
I am a person
with a sense of humor.
Peter, I want you
to come home.
No. No, I,
I can't leave Casey
right now. He needs me.
(MOUTHING) No, way.
LIZZIE: I'm your wife.
I need you.
Do you?
I mean, you got Andie.
I don't know where
I fit in here anymore.
She's just using
me for my uterus.
LIZZIE:
Oh, my God!
What is it, Lizzie?
Nothing!
Just forget it, okay?
See,
you always do that.
I do what?
You shut down.
that's what happens
to me when I feel like
I'm being ganged up on.
No one is
ganging up on you.
That's how it feels.
All right,
no one can make
you feel anything, Lizzie.
Oh, that is
such bullshit.
Good, Lizzie,
good. Get...
Fuck off, Peter!
Don't tell me
what to do!
You know, it might not
look like it right now,
but she has
just had a breakdown.
A breakthrough,
breakthrough.
Oh, paging Doctor Freud.
(CHUCKLING)
Oh, yeah!
(SNIFFLING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Oh, gosh.
Hey, Justin.
What's up?
Oh, okay. I'm,
I'm sorry, what time is
your soccer match?
Oh, okay, fine.
So why don't we play it...
Why don't we just
play it by ear?
Hello? Hello?
Oh, goddamn it!
Jesus! I didn't realize
she was so full of rage.
Hmm.
Oh, it's always been there.
It's just been
buried deep down.
Oh, you're
goddamned right!
I'm full of rage.
I had plans!
Plans!
Okay, well,
so I'm going
to head back to work.
How convenient.
What?
You can't smoke.
Oh, fuck off!
Hey.
I'm sorry if you felt
ganged up on.
But we all had plans.
Yeah?
What were yours?
It's just,
I think it's just the latch,
you know.
Yes.
You just do that
and it just closes.
because, look,
see, it's bent
and doesn't close.
Okay, don't try
and sucker me,
all right?
I'm not, ma'am.
I'm telling you,
this is broken.
And with the labor
for the gate...
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Why are you speaking
to me in Spanish?
Because  no sono un idiota ,
that's why.
I can understand
everything you're saying.
You can?
Yes, I am American.
Okay, fine, forget it.
Forget it.
Look, look.
I'll fix this myself.
Fine. Fine.
Look, see?
It doesn't close.
See? Look,
see it opening?
It's closing, right?
It doesn't close.
You want to fix it?
You fix it.
Ow!
ANDIE: Are you okay?
Yeah.
What can I do?
Nothing.
I don't need anything.
I'm an independent
woman now, remember?
Ow!
Lizzie!
You know it's great
not having to rely on men.
This is just
so much more
preferable.
It's not like the gate
was getting fixed when
there were men living here.
That's not the fucking point.
(MUG SHATTERING)
Oh, fuck!
Fuck!
Fuck, shit!
Joyce!
LIZZIE: Hey, Andie!
Where do you
think you're going?
You're scaring her.
You give her back
right now!
No way!
Not when you're like this.
There should be
a social services for dogs.
Oh, yeah? There is.
It's called
the ASPCA, Einstein.
ANDIE: My God.
(MIMICKING LIZZIE) Einstein.
Okay.
This is it.
You can build
anything you want here.
Your dream house awaits.
I mean, breathe it in.
You know, just.
(INHALES)
Really savor it.
Let your imagination
go wild.
Ah, I don't want to build
a fucking house.
Plus, it's way
too much work.
You're not going
to build it, all right?
Builders will build it.
Do you hear the sound
of those jack hammers
out there?
That is the sound of other
people's dreams
being constructed.
It's loud.
Wait.
Hey, come on, buddy,
you're reaching.
You don't wanna reach
around on me.
Anyway, the only
jack hammering I do
is in the bedroom.
Right, baby?
(GIGGLES)
(BABBLING)
Baby, I'm hungry.
All right, titties,
let's go get you some food.
Ooh!
(STUTTERING)
I'm sorry.
Heather, is it?
Feather.
Right, Feather.
Right. I just thought
you'd really like this area,
considering you love
hiking and there are
so many trails nearby.
Oh, yeah. When we were all
at that house in Mulholland,
you said, "I love to hike".
And I thought, well...
What is he talking about?
I'm sorry. I just realized
that wasn't you,
that was another girl.
It's funny,
now that I look at you.
Yeah, you look
nothing like her!
Foot in mouth.
This is my bad.
Oh, man!
PETER:
I got to take pictures,
that's what I got to do.
Ciao,  bella.
Goddamn it!
You piece of shit!
(GRUNTS)
You man whore!
Ugh, fuck you! Fuck you!
Come on.
Hey.
Yeah.
Mmm.
Hey, Joyce.
Wow.
You look really big.
Yeah.
Growing strong.
No, I mean,
you're really big.
You're fucking huge.
Wish I could say
the same about you.
Wow!
It's not as good
without the curly straw.
Yeah, no shit.
Can I ask you a question?
Yeah, shoot.
Heroin?
Ha.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
I, uh.
if maybe you, kind of felt
like maybe you weren't
good enough your whole life
'cause your mom
gave you up.
I know
that's kind of
a personal question.
Yeah, kind of.
So, is that
how you feel?
I don't know.
Sometimes.
Depends on the day.
You shouldn't smoke.
Yeah, well,
you shouldn't have
swallowed the.
Believe me, man,
I'm fucking
happy about it.
(CELL PHONE CHIMING)
Yep, it's past my curfew.
All right.
Well, I'll see you around.
Yeah.
This was nice.
Yeah, it was.
Let's go, Joyce.
Let's go back to crazy town.
CASEY:
Bye, Joyce.
(GATE CREAKING)
Oh, fuck!
(SIGHS)
(TV PLAYING)
Hey.
No, I don't want any pasta.
When are you going to get
your own place?
The problem is,
I don't want
a fucking roommate, Peter.
I want you to leave.
Where were you just now?
Don't. Peter,
I'm warning you.
Look, I just don't know
where this is coming from.
Hey, don't put
that shit on the couch, man.
I sit here on your crumbs
and your fucking toenails.
Put it on the coffee table.
All right, you are really
amped up right now,
you know that?
And that's not
a coffee table,
it's an end table, okay?
What concerns me.
Casey!
(BOTH STRUGGLING)
I'm so sick
of your fucking shit.
Fuck! Fuck!
Get the fuck off me!
Get off of me!
Get out.
I'm sorry.
Pack your shit up
and leave before
I fucking burn it.
LIZZIE:
♪ Down in the valley
♪ Valley so low
♪ Late in the evening
♪ Hear the train blow
(BELL DINGS)
♪ Down in the valley
♪ Valley so low
♪ Late in the evening
♪ Hear the train blow
♪ The train is gone, love
♪ And out of sight
♪ Good night, my darling
♪ Darling, good night
♪ Good night
ANDIE: Hey.
You look nice.
Um.
I'm just going out
for a little while.
I miss my friend.
Yeah. All right, well,
I'll see you in a bit.
What's wrong?
Does my breath stink?
Ow.
Oh, babe,
that looks infected.
No. It's fine.
Okay.
I'm gonna have a shower.
You know, maybe
we should split up.
Okay. I'll call you
in a sec.
Andie, what happened?
How did she get out?
How? The gate was open.
Yeah, well,
did you leave it open?
No. I've been home
all day.
ANDIE:  Lizzie?
Lizzie, are you there?
Look, maybe
Joyce got out
some other way.
Yeah, um, I got to go.
Joyce?
Joycey?
ANDIE:  Joyce?
PETER: I can barely see
anything. Maybe
we should call it a night.
I wanna keep looking.
Lizzie,
someone will see her tags.
Okay, I'm, I'm gonna
keep looking.
but I got a real early meeting
tomorrow, so.
I waited for you.
Lizzie.
I just don't understand
why you married me
when you knew
I wanted children someday.
I thought someday
I'd want them, too.
I got to go.
Lizzie.
Lizzie, wait.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello? (SNIFFS)
CASEY: Did you just drool
on yourself?
PETER: No, no,
I spat on the floor.
Oh, that's nice.
I'm good.
PETER: All right, man,
sorry to bother you.
I didn't mean
to waste your time,
but I'm gonna drive. I'm good.
Peter, give me
your fucking keys.
No, I'm. Don't worry
about it. I'm gonna drive.
Peter...
Let me see your keys.
You want to see them?
Okay? Ow, ow, ow!
All right!
Come on,
come on.
Friggin' maniac.
Atta boy.
You're driving me tomorrow
to pick it up.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, early.
Really early.
I'm gonna be up and at 'em.
I'm not joking man.
I know you're not,
you're not gonna get up.
You're serious.
You're not gonna get up.
You don't even lock
this piece of shit?
CASEY: Get in.
Weirdo.
Atta boy.
Hey, you see that bartender?
Yeah, he was
really into you.
No! She! The girl. Ah.
There we go.
Open that, bud.
What's the matter with you?
I'm in the dark.
You had trouble getting in?
(LAUGHING)
Hey. You okay?
I fucked up.
I'm like a douchebag.
Man, you're
not a douchebag.
Yeah, I am.
I don't know
when that happened.
Hey, man.
We're all doing
the best we can.
Hey,
You wanna get a beer?
I'm just messing
with you, bro.
(LAUGHS)
No!
(VOMITING)
Fuck! Peter!
Oh, man!
Fuck you.
You are a douchebag.
(GROANS)
Ow.
Joyce?
Oh, my God.
(WOOFS)
You've got my dog.
(CHUCKLES)
Joyce.
Knock it off.
(MAN CHUCKLING)
Oh, sweetie, are you okay?
Whoa!
How do we know
it's your dog?
Just, look at her tags.
It says Joyce.
Honey.
That's a lucky guess.
It says Joyce,
but how do you spell it?
Are you kidding?
(PETER VOMITING)
Oh, Jesus, man.
PETER: Fuck.
I've never seen anyone
puke so much,
not even in detox.
Oh, yeah. Yeah!
Yeah, don't hold back.
Come on, I want to see
where this is going.
Why did you leave
your gate open?
Yeah?
Yeah, we're
gonna call
the animal people.
The people
that are in charge
of animals.
They're half animal,
half people.
It would be terrible
if they were in charge.
If half animal, half people
were in charge of animals.
Well, I mean
if they had people brains.
Oh. Argh.!
It's Lizzie,
I'll call you back.
Fuck! Lizzie!
Come on, we're
not ready to throw
in the towel here.
Come on, kid,
get off the ropes.
Give him hell.
Atta boy.
Give me your uppercut.
Use your reach.
Will you please
shut the hell up?
But what if they were, like,
they're in charge
of all the animals
and they were half animal,
half people.
That way they could...
They can decide between,
if there was a dispute
between animals and people.
They're like.
"Well. I'm half of each,
so I'll decide".
I don't even know
what you're talking about.
This is such
a smart idea.
This is a smart idea.
Can I just take my dog?
Again, this is our dog.
We will help you
find your dog.
We will track
your dog down for you.
Let's track him down.
Give me back
my fucking dog!
BOTH: Whoa!
That came out
of nowhere, man.
Come on, Joyce.
Bye, Joyce.
Right at the same time.
Are you kidding me?
Yeah, we are like
two peas in a...
We're bros.
Two pieces
of a pizza.
Pizza.
(SIGHING) Oh, dude,
that was awesome.
No, seriously.
I can't wait
for the next round.
Why do you have
a geriatric stool
in your shower?
That's how I sit here
and wash my balls.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Think about life.
You don't do that?
Hey.
Yo. What up, dog?
Wait, what?
Oh, it hurts.
CASEY: Come on.
You guys.
Come on.
Here you are.
ANDIE: Wait! Wait!
No way!
I'm not getting
in the middle!
Well, I'm worried
I'm going to throw up.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Peter,
get in the middle!
Okay.
(ANDIE GROANS)
You in?
Yes!
PETER:
Casey, that saves no time!
CASEY: You don't know that.
ANDIE: You stink!
Roll down the window.
ANDIE:
You don't have electric?
PETER: I was drinking.
That's why it smells.
ANDIE: Ew! Am I just,
like, sitting in vomit?
PETER: Signal.
Use your signal!
LIZZIE:
♪ Violets loved you
♪ Angels love heaven.
♪ And Joyce I love you
LIZZIE: Andie?
Whoo!
There's somebody here
who wants to see you!
She must be asleep, Joyce.
(SCREAMING)
I'm gonna barf.
Don't barf.
Keep it in.
Oh, my God!
The baby is crowning!
Two biggest pussies
in the world.
My pussy's about to get big
in a fucking second,
motherfucker!
That's it, girl, come on.
Push it out, Andie.
That's it. That's it, girl.
That's it, that's it,
that's it.
Come on, keep pushing.
Keep pushing.
Push it out.
That's it, girl.
That's it.
Oh, shit.
Shit.
Honestly, I don't think
you guys would have gotten
through that without me.
Everyone's fine.
Baby is healthy.
Andie is resting.
It's a boy.
Wow.
You can see her now.
Hey.
(WHISPERING)
I'm so sorry I wasn't here.
(SIGHS)
I found Joyce.
Oh, good.
Hey.
Hey, little guy.
Yeah.
Wow.
(BABY WHIMPERS)
Yeah.
He's a feisty
little boy.
I can't believe
he's finally here.
Lizzie,
I didn't know
it was gonna
feel this way.
I'm sorry.
I hope one day
you'll find it in your heart
to forgive me.
Hey.
What's up?
CASEY: Wow.
I thought it
would look more
like an alien.
Nice.
What? I'm saying
it doesn't look like an alien.
CASEY: It's a compliment.
PETER: Okay fine,
whatever.
CASEY:
You know, just relax.
Try not to puke, okay?
PETER: Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that joke's
not getting old.
CASEY: No.
No, it's not actually.
Don't touch it You're
gonna contaminate it.
Okay.
You should probably leave.
Should we put him in a room
or something?
Okay, thank you.
Tres bien.
(CRYING)
LIZZIE:  So, I saw Peter
the other day.
DR. GRAYSON:
Oh, what happened?
LIZZIE:
Well, we laughed a lot.
I can't remember the last time
we laughed that much.
And he told me
how proud he was of Casey,
and of me.
I guess I just couldn't see
what was happening before,
or maybe
I just didn't want to see it.
I saw it.
Oh?
So, why didn't you
say anything?
It wasn't my place.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Did that hurt?
This?
Yeah.
Ah.
Over time.
So it's really not that bad.
Do it gradual.
Just relax.
You'll be fine.
(SIGHS)
Okay.
Want a shot
of tequila?
Do it.
LIZZIE: Fuck! Oh, fuck!
What do you think
of that, Joyce?
She likes it.
Uh, I'm gonna go,
but I'll see you next week.
Okay. See you, Justin.
Hi.
Come on, Joyce.
Hello, Joyce.
Say hi.
How are you doing?
(SIGHS)
(BABY COOING)
Wow.
I don't think we ever got
a formal introduction.
Right.
This is Gus.
So big.
I know.
He's like
a giant mutant.
So, how's it going?
Pretty fucking hard,
actually.
Yeah?
Yeah, I had to
move back in
with my dad.
Hmm.
It's,
It's been all right.
He, um,
he really loves
being a grandpa.
Well, that's great.
So, how about you?
Me?
Um,
I'm considering
my options.
It's going to be
one lucky kid.
(BABY COOING)
Hey.
I really should
get him home
for his nap, so.
Well, we're
going that way.
Come on, Joyce.
Come on.
Let's go visit.
Are you
okay there?
Yeah.
Okay.
Good dog.
So, um.
ANDIE: Is Justin
legal yet?
(LIZZIE LAUGHS)
He's got another
couple of weeks.
ANDIE: Yeah?
Send him
my way.
I will.
His French
is very, very good.
Getting better
all the time.
Action's a little
slow these days.
I'm happy to go
a little bit younger.
Well, you gotta do
what you gotta do.
You know,
I think my dad's
new girlfriend
is actually younger
than Justin.
Oh, my God.
Do you know
that they actually have
a kid on the way?
(GASPING) No way.
No, really. It's weird,
because I don't know if she's
sure how babies get made.